frad.co 2018-08-31

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out the basis on which we will process any personal information we collect from you, or that you provide to us. Please read the following carefully.

Information we may collect about you:

We may collect and process the following information about you:

Information you give us. You may give us information by filling in forms on our site or by corresponding with us by phone, e-mail or otherwise. This includes information you provide when you register to use our site, search for a product, place an order on our site, participate in the frad.co, enter a competition, promotion or survey, and when you report a problem with our site. The information you give us may include your name, address, e-mail address and phone number, financial and credit card information.

The following information may be collected, but will be anonymised and will not contain any information from which you can be identified:

• Technical information, including the Internet protocol (IP) address of your computer, your login information, browser type and version, time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform; and

• Information about your visit, including the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through and from our site (including date and time); products you viewed or searched for; page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page and any phone number used to call our customer service number.

How we use your personal information

Personal information you provide is used by us only for the following purposes:

• To improve your shopping experience at our website

• To process your order

• With your permission, to notify you of products or special offers that may be of interest to you

Sharing of information

We do not sell or otherwise share your information with any third party. We use your information exclusively as stated within this Policy.

Disclosure of your information

We may share your personal information with members of frad.co's group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries.

If we sell or buy any business or assets, we may disclose such information to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets as may reasonably be required.

Where we store your information

All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Any payment transactions will be encrypted using SSL technology. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet may not be completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to prevent unauthorised access.

Cookies

We use cookies to keep track of your current shopping session so that you may retrieve your shopping basket at any time, and to personalise the contents our website as well as to ensure a consistent experience. We also use cookies to track how visitors interact with our website to monitor how we are performing.

No personally identifiable information is stored in these cookies.

For the full technical explanation, read more about cookies used on our site.

If you wish to remove these cookies, you can do so by following these instructions.

Emails

We hate junk mail too!

We will email you to process your order and afterwards to introduce you to the benefits of our loyalty programme. Only frad.co will use your email address. We will never pass on your email address or personal information to a third party for marketing purposes. We will provide your email address to delivery services for the sole purpose of sending you tracking notifications for your delivery.

You can unsubscribe any time

When you join the frad.co email newsletter, you can unsubscribe at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link that is at the bottom of every message that we send. Or you can send a message to our customer care department and we will unsubscribe you.

Links to other websites

Our site may contain links to other web sites that are not owned or operated by us. We do not control, recommend or endorse and are not responsible for these sites or their content, products, services or privacy policies. Please refer to the privacy policy of the third party web site for guidance on the operation, function and management of that web site. You should also independently assess the authenticity of any website which appears or claims that it is one of our sites (including those linked to through an email).

Changes to this policy

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our privacy policy and how they affect you.

Your rights  
The Data Protection Act (the "Act") has various provisions which ensure that any person who has access to your personal information must comply with strict rules.

The Act provides the following principles, which we follow at all times:

• We will process your data fairly and lawfully.

• We will obtain your data only for specified and lawful purposes, and shall not use it for any other purpose.

• We will ensure that personal data held shall be adequate, relevant and not excessive in relation to the purpose for which it is held.

• We will ensure that personal data shall be accurate and, where necessary, kept up to date.

• We will ensure that personal data shall not be kept for longer than is necessary for that purpose.

• We will ensure that personal data shall be processed in accordance with your rights under the Act.

• We will take appropriate technical and organisational measures to protect any personal data from any destruction, damage or loss.

• We will not transfer your personal data outside the European Economic Area unless that country or territory ensures an adequate level of protection.

Contact us

Any questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and you can [email us](http://www.frad.co/contacts) at through our "Contact Us" page.
